Medical expenses continue to rise each
year and we all face a difficult choice.
Private health care, which is relatively
expensive, or public health care, where
waiting times are very long. Is it your
only option to wait in pain or drain
your savings? Beyond major medical
needs, many people are increasingly
turning to Chinese medicine,
acupuncture, and physiootherapy for
wellness and preventive care. However,
these services often fall into a
coverage gap. The Sunlife Sun Plus term
life insurance plan offers access to a
wide range of medical and health care
services with exclusive discounts
together with an annual premium of just
$198.2
Hong Kong dollars and no medical
underwriting required. It includes a
$5,000 Hong Kong dollars compassionate
benefit and features SunPass, which
provides access to designated medical
and healthcare services at discounts of
up to 50% with unlimited usage including
consultations with Chinese and Western
medicine practitioners, acupuncture,
bone setting, physiootherapy, dental
care, and more. For example, Miss Sun
uses some pass to consult Chinese
medicine practitioners, undergo
acupuncture treatments, and receive
dental scaling services. Each visit can
cost as little as slightly over 200 Hong
Kong dollars. And after the discounted
rate, she may claim the expenses through
her company's medical insurance, meaning
she may not need to pay anything out of
pocket. Looking to ease the pressure of
rising medical costs? Worry no more.
Enroll in the Sum Plus term life
insurance plan today to enjoy savings
and greater peace of mind for yourself
and your family.